thesmartphoneappreview.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third-party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, The Smartphone App Review has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third-party advertisers.

**Affiliate Disclosure  
**We may be an affiliate for some of the products, services, and companies listed on The Smartphone App Review, meaning compensation may have been received in some form to promote that app or company. Some posts on the site may also be sponsored, meaning compensation was given to research and write about that app or service. These posts will be disclosed as such. However, the compensation received does not affect the reviews as it is a guarantee of a review, not of the content of the review. We will be just as honest with these reviews as we would any other. This is also stated on our [contact page](http://thesmartphoneappreview.com/contact-us/).

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting The Smartphone App Review, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third-party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of The Smartphone App Review then you may contact us at simon.burns78@gmail.com
